<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ricardo.angeli</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ricardo.angeli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rangeli.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>6502 on FPGA: Part I - The ALU Awakens</title>
      <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2016-01-26-mos-fpga-alu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2016-01-26-mos-fpga-alu/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          What&amp;rsquo;s an ALU? ALU stands for Arithmetic Logic Unit. It is a device that takes one or two numerical values, performs an arithmetic operation, and then outputs the result. Operations can range from addition to bitwise functions such as OR, XOR, or AND. It&amp;rsquo;s the heart within the processor architecture. Modern processor architectures may include multiple ALUs, but the 6502 keeps it simple with just one.
The 6502 ALU The implementation of the ALU in the 6502 is simple and only contains what&amp;rsquo;s absolutely necessary, which is great for our efforts in modeling its behavior.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6502 on FPGA: An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2016-01-25-mos-fpga-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2016-01-25-mos-fpga-intro/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Introduction to the Introduction So during the fall semester 2015, I took an FPGA design class as a technical elective at university. I discovered through the various projects and assignments that I really enjoyed working with FPGAs and addressing the challenges that come with programming logic and thinking in parallel. So to continue this path, I planned out a semester of independent study during spring 2016 where I work on a project where I design my own microprocessor from scratch on an FPGA.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create an Assembly-Only Project for TIVA Launchpad in Code Composer</title>
      <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2015-03-04-how-to-create-assembly-only-project-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 06:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2015-03-04-how-to-create-assembly-only-project-for/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Baremetal ARM? Time to don the geek glasses!    Aargh! You have no idea how long I spent googling keywords contained in the title of this post. &amp;nbsp;Especially now that you found this post, you lucky duck. &amp;nbsp;I wasted literal DAYS trying to get a stupid assembly program to run on my TIVA Connected Launchpad. &amp;nbsp;I&#39;ve done a handful of programs for the TIVA in the past, but they have been all in C and all the examples TI gave were also in C.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from the Dead!</title>
      <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2015-03-03-back-from-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 05:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2015-03-03-back-from-dead/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Me after long coding sessionSo way back in my freshman year of college, I felt inspired and decided to create my own electronics blog!
Then I just kinda forgot about it.
A lot has happened since and I&#39;ve worked on many projects. &amp;nbsp;I&#39;m still in college, but I can finally see the light at the end of the tunnel!
Anyway, I&#39;m going to be making a few posts here about some stuff I&#39;ve been working on.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn off TV&#39;s with an Arduino</title>
      <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2011-09-22-turn-off-tvs-with-arduino/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 23:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2011-09-22-turn-off-tvs-with-arduino/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Behold, my artistic talents!!
&#39;Bout it:
This little build will go through several manufacturer&#39;s TV codes for turning off (or on) nearly any kind of television. &amp;nbsp;It does take a while to go through the program so depending on how weird your TV is, it might take up to a minute to find the right code--though it does my Samsung in about 2 seconds.
Yeah, I know. &amp;nbsp;It&#39;s like that &#34;
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2011-09-22-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 20:17:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rangeli.github.io/posts/2011-09-22-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          My name is Ricardo Angeli and I&#39;m a freshman studying Computer Engineering at the University of Central Florida. &amp;nbsp;I created this blog to track down some of the electronic crap I&#39;ve made and what I&#39;m currently working on as well as stuff that&#39;s happening in my life. Now as you may have noticed, this blog is called &#34;Ricky&#39;s Amateur Electronics&#34;. &amp;nbsp;There is a reason: I&#39;m just starting out playing around with microcontrollers, servos, resistors, etc.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>